A Guide to the Virginia Place Name Society Records, 1947-1982
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Place Name Survey of Virginia Files, 1958-1981., Extent: 19 boxes. (Box 39-57)
  - Field Operations - Arlington - Augusta, 1974-1976. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Field Operations - Bedford - Buckingham, 1969-1981. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Field Operations - Campbell - Cumberland, 1974-1978. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Field Operations - Dinwiddie - Essex, 1974-1976. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Field Operations - Fairfax - Frederick, 1971-1980. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Field Operations - Giles - Greene, 1970-1979. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Field Operations - Halifax - King William, 1974-1979. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Field Operations - Lancaster - Lunenburg, 1974-1980. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Field Operations - Madison (Grid Map), 1978. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Field Operations - Madison, 1973-1975. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Field Operations - Madison, 1976-1980. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Field Operations - Mathews, 1974-1978. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Field Operations - Mecklenburg - Nottoway, 1973-1979. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Field Operations - Orange - Pulaski, 1974-1977. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Field Operations - Stafford - York, 1974-1979. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Field Operations - Chesapeake - Richmond, 1972-1978. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Field Operations - Bridges, Forests, Parks, Highways, etc., 1975-1980. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Field Operations - Virgina (General), 1978. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Publications and Forms - Goals of the Survey. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Publications and Forms - Procedures, 1972-1974. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Publications and Forms - Approved Place Names Index, 1974. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Publications and Forms - Gloucester County, 1979. (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
  - Publications and Forms - Greene County. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Publications and Forms - Mathews County, 1978-1979. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Publications and Forms - Brochures, Maps, etc. 1969-1979. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Publications and Forms - Institutional Publications. (Box 46, Folder 1-5)
  - Publications and Forms - Topographical Map Publications. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Publications and Forms - Map Indexes (Accomack - King and Queen). (Box 47)
  - Publications and Forms - Map Indexes (King George - Suffolk). (Box 48)
  - Publications and Forms - Topographic Maps. (Box 49)
  - Card Files - Place Names (By County). (Box 50)
  - Card Files - Approved Names by United States Board on Geographic Names. (Box 51)
  - Card Files - Post Office Names. (Box 52)
  - Card Files - Post Office Names (By County). (Box 53)
  - Card Files - Greene and Madison Counties. (Box 54)
  - Card Files - Madison County (Map Indexes). (Box 55)
  - Card Files - Speech Notes. (Box 56)
  - Card Files - Bibliography, Correspondents. (Box 57)